Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/duy-thinhnguyen-a30145266 (LinkedIn) thinhsuy.github.io/ VisualPage_Web/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Multi-agent Systems
Leading Development Teams
Recommendation System

Languages

Vietnamese (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Advanced Learning Algorithms
Unsupervised Learning,
Recommenders, Reinforcement
Learning

Upper-Intermediate English Training HIPAA Associate (HIPAAA)

Publications

Attention Light Graph Memory Network for Medical Recommendation System

Duy Thinh Nguyen

Al/ML Engineer | Data Scientist Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I have 2 years' experience in generative AI and healthcare. And 4 years to graduate with a major of Data Science at University of Science - VN National University.

I have found a lot of interest in AI Engineer and more focus on solutions based on GenAI for healthcare problems.

Although I'm focusing in engineering, I'm still engaging in research endeavors, including paper contributions and research publication. Beside the hand on with modeling, I still experience several related requirements, e.g Prompt Engineer, ML Operation, CI/CD, MySQL, Vector Database, Docker and Kubernetes, ReactJS (for production).

Experience

AIAIVN

AI/ML Team Lead September 2024 - Present (7 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Lead a team of Al Engineers to hand on Chat-Bot Assistant for difference industries, including Tourist-Traveling, Banking and Healthcare.

KMS Technology, Inc.

1 year 6 months

AI/ML Engineer

August 2023 - September 2024 (1 year 2 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

As in a Innovation Lab team, I defined the state of the art technicals of GenAl to solve problems of healthcare, defining architecture, building PoCs and consulting to chief officers, e.g. CTO, CEO, President, ...

Work with different team:

- Work with HR team to interview and recruit many candidates;
- Work with Training team to run as Mentor/Advisor/Trainer for several Al engineer interns.

- Work with clients as AI Engineer Consultant to support many ideas on production.
- Work with Media Team as Speaker to sharing ideas of generative Al solutions for many conferences.

Research Intern

April 2023 - August 2023 (5 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

We build RAG from scratch and deal with the complex structure of healthcare data. We are also trained with significant policies in the healthcare domain and blend them into research Proof of Concept (PoC) for health providers with GenAI.

STEMpedia

Teaching Assistant

February 2023 - July 2023 (6 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Teaching Assistant about Adruino and ML for IoTs

Education

VNUHCM - University of Science

Bachelor of Science - BS, Data Science · (August 2020 - August 2024)

University of Nevada-Las Vegas

Bachelor's degree, International Economics Law (April 2019 - July 2020)